### NIRVAN ADAM PRAMUDHYTA

nirvan.pramudhyta@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/nirvanadam/ | https://nirvanadam.vercel.app/

+62 812 1524 4015 | Wonosobo, Central Java 56314

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Bachelor's degree graduate in Informatics Engineering with a GPA of 3.76, actively engaged in both academic and non-academic activities, and successfully completed studies in 3.5 years. Possesses freelance experience as a Junior Frontend Developer in a Software Development company and contributed actively as a committe member of the Web Division in the campus computer club. These experiences have strengthened skills in programming, web development, project management, communication, teamwork, and problem-solving. Committed to building a successful career in the technology and digital industry with a strong willingness to continuously learn and deliver the best contributions in a professional environment.

#### **EDUCATION**

Universitas Dian Nuswantoro • Semarang, Central Java Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering

2020 - 2024

GPA: 3.76 / 4.00

#### **PROJECTS**

NgajiAja ● React.js, Tailwind CSS, Shadcn, React Query ● https://ngajiaja.com/ ● https://bit.ly/repo-ngajiaja

Application of guidance and mentoring programs for learning the Qur'an from basic, tahsin, tahfidz in a private, friendly and free of charge (donations as much as possible).

- Developed responsive UI/UX with React.js, Tailwind CSS, and Shadon and ensure optimal display on various devices.
- Collaborated with the Backend team to integrate APIs for landing pages, dashboards, and authentication features.
- Implemented React Query for efficient state management.

Taskify • React.js, Tailwind CSS, Redux • https://adam-taskify.vercel.app/ • https://bit.ly/repo-taskify

A simple and efficient to-do list app that helps organize tasks, stay productive and track progress with ease.

- Design modular and reusable components to improve development efficiency.
- Design and implement responsive UI/UX using Tailwind CSS and optimized across devices.
- Implemented Redux as state management to efficiently manage state and CRUD functions.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Black Wolf Tech Indonesia • Bandung, West Java

Agt 2023 - Now

# Junior Frontend Developer (Freelance Project Based)

- · Developed NgajiAja app interface using React.js, Tailwind CSS, and Shadon, improving responsiveness and ease of navigation for users.
- Collaborated with the Backend team to integrate APIs and optimize data synchronization.
- Performed debugging using Chrome DevTools and improved application stability.

Binar Academy • South Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Feb - Jun 2023

## Team Lead Frontend Developer (Final Project Bootcamp)

- · Lead the Frontend team, provide technical direction, and ensure effective communication to achieve project goals.
- Manage team tasks using Trello, monitor progress, and resolve development bottlenecks.
- Conduct code reviews to ensure quality, consistency, and adherence to Frontend development standards.

### ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dian Nuswantoro Computer Club ● Semarang, Central Java

Jul 2022 - Jul 2023

- Web Division Committe
  - Contribute to the development of the organization's website to support internal operations.
  - Plan, organize, and coordinate activities and work programs to support organizational goals.
  - Develop and deliver web development training materials covering HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, to improve participants' understanding and skills in web development.

# HARD SKILLS

- Programming Language: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL
- Frameworks & Libraries: React.js, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Axios
- Development Tools: Git, GitHub, Vite, Postman, MySQL
- Office Tools: Microsoft Office, Google Workspace

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Team Collaboration
- Adaptability
- Project Management
- Creativity
- Attention to Detail
- Critical Thinking

Problem Solving